Morning Ashish, first of all let's
talk about the news stocks. Some results have come
and there is some news as well. There are triggers too.
Tell me what to eat today. Good morning
Deepanshu. First of all, let's look at the events. The
results will come today. I am telling you that the results of
ICC Lombard and Cash in Tata
Coffee, Saffron India Australia Solutions
and Crisil will come here. The focus will be
here.
Apart from this, keep a special eye on Jeans Tenless stock
because there is a board meeting where the
special dividend will be considered.
Mirza International, if you
look till now, was trading in the T group,
now it will be transferred to A group again. A
new listing is going to happen.
You are seeing a lot of action in the primary market.
Avallon Technology
's issue got a subscription of about 2.34 times. The
issue price was 436.
Now if you look here, it will be listed today.
You will see an adjustment in some stocks.
Muthoot Finance.
Look here, the internal dividend of ₹22,
you will see its adjustment in the stock price.  It will
get it and if
you look at the logistics sector here, then the
terminals sector and the demerger of Transion Trans India
Realty, a company, can
also be seen here. The dividend date can also be seen here.
If you look at Apple here also,
because the first retail store is going to be
launched in BKC, Mumbai.
Tim Cook is already in India.
He also held a briefing with the media yesterday.
If you look at it, as you
mentioned, there are some results too. So
keep an eye on Angel One here because the results are quite
good. You have seen an increase of 21% in income. The
operating profit is
30% bigger and the good thing is that there is
expansion in margin as well, from about 43% to 46%
and you have seen a growth of about 11% in profit as well.
Overall good results.
Along with this, there is also a dividend of ₹4. Just
dial, if you look here also, then the results are quite
good. I mean, you have seen an increase of 40%. The
profit of the company has increased from Rs 6 crore to
about Rs 34 crore.  It has increased and if we
look at the profit on one hand, it has increased by about 280%, that is, it has
increased from Rs 22 crore to Rs
84 crore. The results of Quick Hill are
not good because if you see,
last year where the operating profit was Rs 35 crore,
this time there has been an operating loss of about Rs 16-17 crore, the
margin has gone
into negative and if we talk about overall profit, then
till last year the profit was around Rs 28 crore,
this time there has been a loss of Rs 6 crore, so
see here the result of Quick Hill is
very weak. Now if we talk about
news, then from today you should watch
Jubilant Foodworks, this stock should be on your radar
because the company
is their associate company which provides
ordering platform and loyalty platform to restaurants.
A big investment came here from Coca-Cola
India, where they have bought 15%
stake, but
even after buying this stake, if you see, the equity
dilution was not as much as the
earlier stake of Jubilant Foodworks,
about 35%. Now this
equity relation is for this because the new
Investors are coming in, due to which in 2019,
their stake will be 75% here.
You will keep an eye on this top. Samvardhana and Performance
International. If you see, their
subsidiary company Yangus and Madrasan Autotech have
bought an additional 30% stake here, so your stake will be around 80%.
Arrest Live Senses has
bought 0.3157%
stake here, so the stake is a little here.
Zee Entertainment also keeps a
special eye on this because see yesterday, a big deal was done.
Today, names of some big investors came out, for example,
if you see,
Morgan Stanley, Goldman Sachs, they
bought the shares and Poonawala Films. You
also saw some deals here yesterday.
Aditya Birla Sun Life and Plutosh
Wealth have bought shares here. So,
some big buyers have come forward
for Zee Entertainment and Punewala Fino. More
action is for you. Thank you very much
Ashish for telling us all these news.